richelieu.com 2016-11-19

# Web Site Security and Privacy Policy

**Richelieu.com Web Site**  
**Security and Privacy Policy**

This Security and Privacy Policy demonstrates our commitment to protect your personal information while you are using the Richelieu Hardware Ltd web site ("Richelieu Hardware") and to ensure that the order confirmation process is secure.

If you choose to use our web site, it means that you agree to our use and collection of your personal information in the manner described herein. If you do not agree with the following, we ask you that you do not use our web site.

**The personal information we collect** Personal information is defined as being information allowing you to be identified as an individual ("personal information"). When you fill out a new account and credit application form and/or an application to obtain an access code to order products on our web site, you need to provide personal information such as your name, your address, your phone number, your e-mail address and other information unique to you. Such personal information remains on our server for the period of time that your account with Richelieu Hardware is active.

When you order products on our web site, you also need to provide your credit card information. However, such information will only be used to pre-authorise payment of your order and will not be transmitted to and kept on our server. 

**Acknowledgment and consent** Richelieu Hardware will only collect personal information that you provide voluntarily. Generally speaking, when you fill out a new account and credit application form and/or an application to obtain an access code, you consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information in order that we can confirm and invoice your order and ship to you the goods you ordered online. Should we need to use your personal information for other purposes, we will again seek your prior consent.

You can revoke your consent at any time, subject to contractual or legal restrictions and by providing a reasonable advance notice. If you wish to revoke your consent at any time, please contact our person in charge of protecting personal information at **(514) 832-4010, ext. 5332** or by sending an e-mail at **InfoWeb@Richelieu.com.** We will then inform you of the consequences, if any, of revoking your consent.

**Privacy of personal information** We respect the privacy of all personal information that we collect on this web site. We will provide access to this personal information only to selected members of our personnel, our representatives and agents, including the vendors that have assisted us in offering the products ordered or for any other purpose described herein. These service providers are bound to protect any personal information that we disclose and to comply with the general principles related to the protection of personal information, as described herein.

**Disclosure of personal information** Richelieu Hardware will never disclose, exchange, lease nor sell your personal information without the prior consent, except in the following circumstances:

We reserve the right to disclose or provide personal information to a third-party if a purchase, a sale, a lease, a merger, an amalgamation or any type of acquisition, disposition or financing proposed or real occurs for the whole or part of Richelieu Hardware or any activity, asset or share of Richelieu Hardware or one of its divisions. This is to ensure that you continue receiving the same product or services or similar ones from the third party.   
We can also disclose your personal information if obligated to do so by a legal obligation, a search warrant, a subpoena or if so ordered or authorized by a court of law.  
We reserve the right to disclosure personal information if, by doing so, it would help us recover monies owed to us by you.

**Security** All personal information that you provide to us online is encrypted using the SSL protocol before being transmitted to our server, or with respect to your credit card information, before being transmitted to a financial institution for the issuance of a pre-authorisation payment number. This measure aims to protect your personal information in order that it may not be intercepted and read in transit. Access to personal information kept on our server is protected by access rights and a password.

**Other information** Richelieu’s goal is to continuously improve the customer’s service. Therefore, Richelieu routinely collects non-personal and non-confidential information mostly coming from mouse clicks and navigation movements during the use of the web site www.Richelieu.com. 

**Scope of the present policy, as it pertains to third-party web sites that can be accessed through the Richelieu Hardware web site**. This present Security and Privacy Policy, as published on this web site, only pertains to the activities of Richelieu Hardware. We cannot be held responsible for any practice related to the protection of personal information by third-party web sites which can be accessed through the Richelieu Hardware web site.

**Review and update of the Security and Privacy Policy** We reserve the right to modify this Security and Privacy Policy, at any time, without prior notice. The Security and Privacy Policy which is published at any time on this web site is to be considered the latest version in effect.

Should you have any questions on the Richelieu Hardware Security and Privacy Policy, please contact our person in charge of protecting personal information at (514) 832-4010, ext. 5332.

Updated on February 1st, 2006
